Notice | [Annual Aquatics Maintenance Shutdown](https://www.cityofgp.com/alerts/annual-aquatics-maintenance-shutdown)

Information | [Fire Restriction Lifted - NO CONDITIONS](https://www.cityofgp.com/alerts/fire-restriction-lifted-no-conditions)

Quick Menu
----------

Search

Search 

Menu

Main navigation
---------------

Mobile Menu
-----------

    Back to Main Menu* [About Grande Prairie](https://www.cityofgp.com/index.php/culture-community/about-grande-prairie)
    Back to Main Menu* [Facilities & Venues](https://www.cityofgp.com/index.php/parks-recreation/facilities-venues)
    Back to Main Menu* [Animals & Pets](https://www.cityofgp.com/index.php/node/85)
    Back to Main Menu* [Budget & Finance](https://www.cityofgp.com/index.php/city-government/budget-finance)
            * [Joint Appeals Board - Subdivision and Development Appeal Board and General Appeals Board](https://www.cityofgp.com/index.php/city-government/mayor-city-council/boards-committees/joint-appeals-board-subdivision-and)
    Back to Main Menu* [Capital Planning and Construction](https://www.cityofgp.com/index.php/roads-transportation/capital-planning-and-construction)
    Back to Main Menu* [About Us](https://www.cityofgp.com/index.php/economic-development/about-us)
    Back to Main Menu* [About Your Property](https://www.cityofgp.com/index.php/business-development/about-your-property)
    Back to Main Menu* [Social Media Directory](https://www.cityofgp.com/index.php/contact-us/social-media-directory)

Search 

Privacy Policy
==============

Privacy Policy
==============

Section navigation
------------------

Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy
------------------------------------------------

All personal information is collected in compliance with section 33 of [Alberta’s Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy Act](http://www.servicealberta.ca/foip/) (FOIP).

### **Transit On-Demand**

Any personal information collected is authorized under Section 33(c) of the _Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy Act, RSA 2000, c. F-25_ (**“FOIP Act”**), as amended from time to time and is managed and protected in accordance with the FOIP Act.  The City of Grande Prairie uses a third-party service provider VIA, who collects your personal information to provide transit booking services.  By clicking the VIA link, you are agreeing to their privacy policy below.  If you have any questions about the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information please contact Steve Harvard at Transit Services at 780-357-7524 or [sharvard@cityofgp.com](mailto:sharvard@cityofgp.com).

* * *

Visitor Tracking
----------------

This website tracks users anonymously with Google Analytics, Siteimprove and Microsoft Clarity. It also uses cookies. The information collected is used to evaluate visitors' use of this website and to compile statistical reports on website activity. You may disable or prevent the use of cookies using your chosen web browsing software. Please note that disabling cookies may interfere with the normal operation of the site.

Remarketing
-----------

This website uses remarketing services to advertise on third party websites to you after you visited our site. We use cookies to serve ads based on your past visits.

Google AdWords remarketing service is provided by Google Inc. via Google Analytics. You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize the Google Display Network ads by visiting the [Google Ads Settings page](http://www.google.com/settings/ads). The [Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) also provides visitors with the ability to prevent their data from being collected by Google Analytics.

Facebook remarketing service is provided by Facebook Inc. You can [learn more about interest-based advertising from Facebook](https://www.facebook.com/help/164968693837950). To opt-out from Facebook’s interest-based ads follow [these instructions](https://www.facebook.com/help/568137493302217) from their website.

External Sites and Services
---------------------------

The City of Grande Prairie is not responsible for the content and privacy practices of other web sites and the City encourages you to examine the terms of use, privacy policy and disclaimer of each site and make your own decisions regarding the disclosure of your personal information and the use of that site.

Security Measures
-----------------

The City of Grande Prairie employs network security measures to monitor for attempts to tamper with information, or to otherwise cause damage. Please be aware that any attempt to damage our systems will be pursued to the maximum extent of the law.

More information
----------------

**For more information on our Terms of Use and Privacy Policies, contact:**

Legal and Risk Management  
City of Grande Prairie  
Postal Bag 4000  
Grande Prairie, Alberta T8V 6V3  
**Telephone:** 780-357-8716

Footer menu
-----------

© City of Grande Prairie

Disclaimer
----------

Google Translate is provided as a free tool to enhance the usability of the City of Grande Prairie website. As such, the City of Grande Prairie is not responsible for Google Translate™.

\>

\>

\>

\>

\>

\>

\>

\>
